Campbell Moroney

Auckland, 1060 | 021 083 38138 | campbellmoroney@gmail.com Github | LinkedIn | ePortfolio

RESUME SUMMARY

Experienced in Node.js and JavaScript based programming with a heavy emphasis in React. Possess strong skills in Agile development that help software development companies deliver effective solutions. Very personable and enjoy working with other members of a team to solve interesting problems. Particularly interested in front-end development, putting my React, Javascript and CSS skills to the test.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- React, Javascript, HTML, CSS, Node.js
- Express, SQL, Docker, AWS, Git, Agile, DevOps, REST API, Jest, Supertest

TECHNICAL PROJECTS

Cat Couture - Github | Site Demo

Comprehensive full-stack React web application for a cat product website

- Uses a PostgreSQL database to store product, discount, and reports information
- Express API server retrieves data from the database and is processed by a fetch request
- Product data is then displayed on a React single page application using best practices
- Utilises JSON Web Tokens and Auth0 for authentication to display product dashboard information

Nested Comments System - Github

Complex fully functional full-stack comments system with likes, comments, editing and deleting

- Uses a local PostgreSQL database populated with Prisma
- Back-end retrieves data from the database and connects this with the front-end React application
- Exhaustive React + Javascript logic using state and hooks to facilitate comments system

Personal ePortfolio - Github | Site Demo

Showcasing UX/UI design and ability with CSS as well as personal projects

- Uses HTML and CSS best practices with website structure and code quality
- Showcases extensive CSS knowledge including animations and scroll behaviour
- Uses JavaScript to facilitate state changes including a contact form and light/dark modes

EXPERIENCE

Labtests Auckland

Medical Laboratory Pre-Analytical Technician

02/2021 - Present

- Maintained a high efficiency in order to facilitate pathology results for thousands of patients per day
- Paid exceptional attention to detail and improved overall workflow in specimen reception
- Ensured correct health and safety protocol by following standard operating procedures in a fast-paced laboratory environment

Browns Boutique Hotel

Queenstown

Assistant Manager

10/2019 - 02/2020

- Oversaw online structuring of the business to an efficient standard
- Managed cleaning staff and ensured stock levels were up to date
- Facilitated guest interaction and kept up the friendly and personable image of the hotel

EDUCATION

Developers Institute

Whangarei

Level 5 Diploma in Web Development & Design [A+]

09/2021 - 09/2022

University of Otago

Dunedin

Bachelor of Science - Pharmacology

02/2017 - 11/2020